<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title></title>
        <link>undefined</link>
        <description>undefined</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 18:27:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Joplin Pages Publisher</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vacation Disaster and harvesting of Haze]]></title>
            <guid>a96dc2c5a7a1418182db5e4564b11f09</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 19:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For our 8 year anniversary we decided to go to Las Vegas and celebrate! I was sure I was prepared, as the automatic watering system was working great! I forgot one little thing however. I forgot to turn on the air conditioner in my office. Since the grow shares space with a few servers, here in Arizona it gets hot quickly, even during the winter. Which means we came home to a sweltering 90f degree office.</p>
<p>This is what we were greeted by:</p>
<img src="/_resources/eaf43d6792c04082af35c0dea3cb84d7.JPG" alt="IMG_8365.JPG" width="814" height="611" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>Haze was very wilted and yellow, and sickly looking. The rest were only marginally better. We put them on a regime of water and they seem to have mostly recovered.</p>
<p>To ensure this doesn't happen again, we invested in a wifi thermometer with an alarm so that I can always keep an eye on the temperature, and hopefully have a friend come by and turn on the AC. 😂</p>
<img src="/_resources/2dec602052724d399041e8cf45375735.JPG" alt="IMG_8423.JPG" width="813" height="1084" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>With that resolved, the next item is checking if Haze is ready for Harvest! The sheet say's we're close, but the only way to really know is to put it under a microscope.</p>
<img src="/_resources/2633a9bc207648d0b48d216571288022.png" alt="2e261cf7d97ccb596c08d173afb92fd9.png" width="872" height="78" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>So that's exactly what we did! Here is the nug we put under the microscope:</p>
<img src="/_resources/8041a93aab244a4b971ed9b3f0813a19.JPG" alt="IMG_8417.JPG" width="776" height="582" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>And here are the photos:</p>
<img src="/_resources/96ab228edd504e1cb6fee432e8cc8110.PNG" alt="IMG_8411.PNG" width="784" height="1165" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<img src="/_resources/8714856886654f518db449d55e27ee2a.PNG" alt="IMG_8410.PNG" width="796" height="1169" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<img src="/_resources/00a11250f01742c08d576c67271a2f53.PNG" alt="IMG_8409.PNG" width="790" height="1168" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<img src="/_resources/53564c933ece43a9be92d39721c96e5e.PNG" alt="IMG_8408.PNG" width="792" height="1180" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>Here she is pre trim, looking pretty shaggy:</p>
<img src="/_resources/06c30f3a6f5445db88201df004e0dbb5.JPG" alt="IMG_8418.JPG" width="819" height="1092" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>And here she is after! Looks much better, and I'm really impressed at how many buds we got! I am guessing we got close to 30 grams from this single plant, but we won't know till after we dry them!:</p>
<img src="/_resources/0e30b04a8372405ca94b1ad297da7a73.JPG" alt="IMG_8420.JPG" width="822" height="1096" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>And here she is, drying in my drying cabinet! Can't wait to weigh the dried buds!</p>
<img src="/_resources/5de31722bb51415ca5fd4b5f066a9a79.JPG" alt="IMG_8422.JPG" width="826" height="1101" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>And here are the rest of the girls, all of them got a nice trim!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/3d2e15bd8ab54489beb04f932fcb9581.JPG" alt="IMG_8424.JPG" width="879" height="660" class="jop-noMdConv" /> <img src="/_resources/36e96b0046d849199d9f901c3fc7b0af.JPG" alt="IMG_8425.JPG" width="909" height="682" class="jop-noMdConv" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Almost Harvest time for Haze]]></title>
            <guid>b483e482f8bd4e80a72221ccc7860974</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 03:48:40 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="/_resources/380bdda0da9c4e52a6d6eece3ba1231d.JPG" alt="IMG_8032.JPG" width="867" height="639" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>As our cannabis cultivation journey progresses, it's essential to pause and evaluate the growth of our plants. Observing Haze, our robust Amnesia strain, we can see significant development in size and structure.</p>
<p>Haze was planted back on September 17th, 2023. We used a mix of Walmart and Amazon soil.</p>
<img src="/_resources/19643d9dc4ab4cd3b07d1ad95495bc2e.JPG" alt="IMG_8031.JPG" width="875" height="1167" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>The key to understanding the perfect harvest time lies in the microscopic examination of trichomes. These minute, crystal-like formations on the bud surfaces hold the secret to maturity and potency.</p>
<p>A close inspection of these trichomes with a magnifying glass reveals much about the plant's status. Clear trichomes suggest that the harvest can wait, as THC levels have not yet peaked. When they adopt a cloudy white hue, it's an indicator of optimal THC concentration, signaling that harvest time is ideal. Trichomes with an amber color are often a sign of diminishing THC potency, indicating a later stage in the plant's lifecycle.</p>
<p>The pistils, too, give us a visual cue. Initially pale and straight, when they darken and curl, it's a visual confirmation of the plant's maturity.</p>
<p>Lastly, the buds themselves should feel dense and sticky to the touch, a tactile sign that they are ripe with resin and ready for harvest.</p>
<p>With that in mind, I took a small clipping from the plant.</p>
<img src="/_resources/be93894e68f041e9815b76f31f4edb4b.JPG" alt="IMG_8034.JPG" width="870" height="653" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>A close inspection of these trichomes with a magnifying glass reveals much about the plant's status. While getting the microscope still and focused enough to take these pictures was difficult, it ended up being definitely worth it. As you can see, many of them are white and milky, I would say about 75-85% of them. We are definitely close!</p>
<p>We are going to give them one more week to mature before harvesting Haze! I look forward to seeing how much weight we get from her!</p>
<img src="/_resources/f8fc3f5118af48eea358341fb60ed667.jpg" alt="2023-11-23-22-20-58-617.jpg" width="869" height="1159" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>Here is another perspective, I've highlighted some of the clearer ones to show why it can still use a bit more time:</p>
<img src="/_resources/c67bfa86dfe3478da762183dc0bcc8b0.jpg" alt="2023-11-23-22-21-19-132.jpg" width="867" height="1156" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>The last is a beautiful explosion of green and white! I love to see these photos!</p>
<img src="/_resources/6b3050eabef546e49a0686f69add3f95.PNG" alt="IMG_8042.PNG" width="872" height="1119" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>And here is my mad microscope lab for reference. You can find that <a title="https://amzn.to/47KTnrG" href="https://amzn.to/47KTnrG">microscope on Amazon for around $32</a>. It's not great, but does work and the photos are acceptable. Getting your photos from the app to your photos however is painfully slow on IOS due to having to save the photo as a file, then converting the file to a photo. But it works and it's cheap so I won't complain too loudly. Those nugs are dispensary provided, and not home grown I'm sad to say.</p>
<img src="/_resources/c03f4f142d9040c8bfe80e8a9a71a2b4.JPG" alt="IMG_8046.JPG" width="877" height="758" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>We have however started work on expanding our grow. I'm excited to see how big of a harvest we can get!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Growing like weeds]]></title>
            <guid>43c7b46a3b4444ce897d8ce73ae13c3c</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="/_resources/e721ff65e18a476aa2bb3b633ca1180a.JPG" alt="IMG_8012.JPG" width="839" height="630" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>The girls are looking great! we are getting ever closer to the smoke date and you can see it with Haze!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Haircut for the ladies]]></title>
            <guid>fc3cac9d49fd4d22b33a2b39fbdb49e0</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 06:37:11 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The ladies got a little trim tonight!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/9f81aa28f2a54ab7a38d6f25b8a1b8cc.png" /></p>
<p>As always, my nesty does an amazing job! The trim looks great and I hope it gives energy to the other buds!</p>
<p>I went ahead and put the link to the spreadsheet I use in the home page to make it easier for myself and others to keep track of my different grows.</p>
<p>Haze is about a month away from Harvest and her buds are looking amazing. Here are some closeups!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/219cb8471f7b4608a33321819e21cbca.JPG" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/15f31c6a8f8c447cab3efbfb5aee3db0.JPG" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/d892164372bc4adeafa9583fe7d420c9.JPG" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Seeds have arrived!]]></title>
            <guid>e38268769c19474fa3bc9c29d8362222</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 16:12:31 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src="/_resources/b092b227f6bd4a62942d528ec31b6fd7.jpg" /></p>
<p>I finally got our order from Seedsman! We ordered the white widow and got the rest for free as a special:</p>
<ul>
<li>White widow
<ul>
<li><img src="/_resources/0ff9e14827f6494689290f99224b79a9.jpg" /></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Alaskan purple auto
<ul>
<li><img src="/_resources/c862184d476e48f79541956b97d48b01.jpg" /></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>OG Kush Auto
<ul>
<li><img src="/_resources/664252244f484a3b8e99571690005e06.jpg" /></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Witches Wedding
<ul>
<li><img src="/_resources/89bbea389aa7410d8d80a6d018fa8b3d.jpg" /></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Here are some photos of the girls from today!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/86141d8f8e9a4051bb200a71718a0c10.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/bd90b405b98c4d11a7970ee89064f3cc.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/8e34983995e04ecbacc0238585754f13.jpg" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automated Water tank refill]]></title>
            <guid>35e882a9aa43408abca6deb4bd7b93ce</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 16:36:54 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src="/_resources/71b0e9c7552049b1bb9d493e7a680fce.jpg" /></p>
<p>The girls are still doing well! Here is their grow schedule:</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/0de74d47ab86452a9478d18ecbbc2a7c.jpg" /></p>
<p>While I was checking on them, I noticed that my watering bag is almost empty! That means we had 8 days of automatic watering. However we did give nutrients (grow big) separately. The automated watering is nice but it’s only really useful when we are gone. While here we give it the nutrients to ensure the buds grow nice and fat.</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/a944176bde034fcdb4b714fea2c3dfde.jpg" /></p>
<p>The girls happy to see their water tower full!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/102181e3be684d0c82d04be911812b04.jpg" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automation Nation]]></title>
            <guid>ec4328be48c341f3b2c324cd001378bb</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 16:44:30 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I was finally able to sit and focus on automating our grow last night! I think the thought of travel has me wanting to ensure that if we do go anywhere, we don't have to rely on relatives to water the plants.</p>
<p>I started first by simply putting the old setup back in place, but immediately noticed that 2 of the 6 outlets were not putting out water. Here is a photo of one of the ones that was working.</p>
<img src="/_resources/4ee43cbe335f4f54b9a8431a07af0ed7.JPG" alt="IMG_7664.JPG" width="803" height="603" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>I figured the issue was related to how long the hose was and how chaotic it was setup. I sat down and began to trim and optimize the path of water for each plant, ensuring that each plant got just enough length of hose to fit in the pot comfortably. Here is a picture of all the hose we were able to avoid using! We removed one outlet as we only needed 5.</p>
<img src="/_resources/d2e40c8c125546d48eb7b7628bd71202.JPG" alt="IMG_7667.JPG" width="586" height="440" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>That left us with this setup!</p>
<img src="/_resources/55257aada7334b4ea68763967966fc8f.JPG" alt="IMG_7668.JPG" width="724" height="543" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>As you can see, I have my 5 gallon water bag on the left, and I have it set to water the plants for 3 minutes every day. Since I'll be home to monitor the output, I plan on adjusting this timing as needed, and every two days manually water in a circular pattern to encourage diverse root growth. I don't want the roots to congregate only around one spot where the drip system is for the whole grow, but at least while I'm traveling or on days I forget it's not a big issue.</p>
<p>As you can see, the nutrient burn is getting better by the day on Haze! I'm flushing the soil out with only water slowly, and it's definitely helping. I think I should be doing a much bigger flush of water, but I don't want to stress the plant too much.</p>
<p>Here is a final picture for today of my babies! As you can see, haze is getting really close! I also took the time to blow the dust out of my fan, it looks a lot cleaner now!</p>
<img src="/_resources/cbed5e2c502d4126b0a0c04d96e7effb.JPG" alt="IMG_7665.JPG" width="845" height="634" class="jop-noMdConv" />]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nutrient Burn and Organization]]></title>
            <guid>ce5e2ca49faa4509afab18e9ef66397d</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 05:47:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I recently realized that some of my stress with growing was not having the information I needed at hand. For example when I needed to harvest, among other things, so being a total nerd, I went ahead and created a spreadsheet. I clipped the notes section, but you get the idea.</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/9e9af7c0f84c4494b0df2bed9f2fe163.png" /></p>
<p>From there, to be able to tie the plant itself to the data, we gave them names and labels.</p>
<img src="/_resources/38858a2678e14f3fb3d56ce86ab465ef.JPG" alt="IMG_7659.JPG" width="512" height="384" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>Which made me feel so good, to see the garden all tagged properly:</p>
<img src="/_resources/5dfe7da9543243c6a3360b417f5c37c9.JPG" alt="IMG_7660.JPG" width="816" height="612" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>With so many plants to care for, I need to get my automatic watering pump back up and running. To that end, I finally DIY'ed a solution to the hose cover that fits perfectly. I had previously put a water gallon lid on the water jug, but it didn't fit well and would fall off, encouraging algae growth. I finally used a sharp blade to cut out the sides of the water cap, and replaced it with the actual lid that came with the jug, but with the spout portion removed. It now looks like this:</p>
<img src="/_resources/1979bf8e688143e5a24c9c1aaa36f526.JPG" alt="IMG_7661.JPG" width="715" height="716" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>One of the other things we've been dealing with as well is nutrient burn. I think I aggressively gave the plants too much nutrients and Haze developed a yellow splotchy color on the leaves. I've gone ahead and switched to only water to flush out the soil, and it seems to be working out great! Photo on the left is from today, and the right is 4 days ago:</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/7c35b93a918c4fcbafa44861416bae1a.png" /></p>
<img src="/_resources/be5680b6ef6a4aa481b729b5193a3680.JPG" alt="IMG_7653.JPG" width="795" height="795" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>Otherwise, the new seedlings are getting along great!</p>
<img src="/_resources/4a20b30fd2eb4a16a1767446ebd6a4f8.JPG" alt="IMG_7654.JPG" width="789" height="828" class="jop-noMdConv" />]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Northern Lights Seedlings!]]></title>
            <guid>7107d10e5854478387557bdb1edf0d4f</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src="/_resources/6ce7752e4b434d2db72020fe797509f0.jpg" /></p>
<p>New little sproutlings!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/b99e5b067d9f4a929a56456c70fa139e.JPG" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amnesia and White Widow Photo Dump and updates!]]></title>
            <guid>02498bb12bc84b4187d35f811a6a3a7f</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 20:33:34 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The plants are growing nicely! Here is a group of photos from the White Widow plant I've started nicknaming Runty:</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/240f3381af544d41933ad3d85e8da693.png" /></p>
<p>When she first started her growth, a piece of the seed stayed on like a hat, but it has since finally fallen off and she is growing great!</p>
<p>All these photos are from the end of Sept until now, the middle of October.</p>
<p>Next up is Amnesia! She's doing great and recently got a trim and we began training her on the netting! Very excited to see the growth!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/a1c2679a727b470a91c93087cc9999be.png" /></p>
<p>And last is Runty's sibling, who is definitely an overachiever:</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/0ac681a0be084dd0b1069e10008ace39.png" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amnesia and White Widow Update]]></title>
            <guid>7d3541e155124d2d8d33cf3dd047f1a4</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 17:45:56 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amnesia is doing good! I think it may still need some more nutrients due to the yellowish sheen, but I think overall it's doing great! Here is a photo from a few days ago</p>
<img src="/_resources/e45c0160384e4be5ba56f9f60225da3e.JPG" alt="IMG_7019.JPG" width="644" height="483" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>And here is one today. As you can see, quite a bit of growth!Pl</p>
<img src="/_resources/a6357048bd3d40d08c42f07c373f1887.JPG" alt="IMG_7252.JPG" width="635" height="846" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>I'm still a bit sad about the loss of our Liberty Haze, but happy that our White Widow seeds are kicking butt! Here are photos from when we transferred the seeds to the trays yesterday:</p>
<img src="/_resources/6efb5eb4a8954b478a7f926931b04b88.JPG" alt="IMG_7249.JPG" width="623" height="467" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p> <img src="/_resources/3c299af89ac948d98c6a0a74cb120b36.JPG" alt="IMG_7251.JPG" width="615" height="820" class="jop-noMdConv" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/5047acad34924908b303dec12c91f55a.JPG" alt="IMG_7250.JPG" width="620" height="826" class="jop-noMdConv" />  <img src="/_resources/0278616aa0a5467b908ff6213ed13380.JPG" alt="IMG_7253.JPG" width="625" height="833" class="jop-noMdConv" /> <img src="/_resources/fb1f3cfed023466ab426af38aba6a640.JPG" alt="IMG_7254.JPG" width="619" height="826" class="jop-noMdConv" /></p>
<p>And here are the seeds today! As you can see, they are ready to rock and roll!</p>
<img src="/_resources/940025d5b98c46a4845f7b4fceeea562.JPG" alt="IMG_7290.JPG" width="642" height="856" class="jop-noMdConv" />]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[White widows transferred to napkin!]]></title>
            <guid>9e47ee0bd13f457888275d28df8a1bbb</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 05:56:54 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Got it done!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/79e7b198f8af4c7080ac14f9ed6739e8.jpg" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Good bye Liberty haze and hello white widow ]]></title>
            <guid>5b40656ae560417cbf69130f71eb1e33</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 15:54:06 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It looks like mold got to the Liberty haze seeds. I think I put too much water in the seedling tray which over saturated the seeds and led to mold growth. RIP.</p>
<p>Lesson learned, now on to white widow, which are our last seeds so we will need to order some more.</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/c38daf70090e456491b390c8a00eff4c.jpg" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Liberty Haze and Amnesia update]]></title>
            <guid>99367b6975034897bde23cc91620abd5</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 16:47:46 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first seed is doing great and I can see it start to sprout in the worm castings:</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/237f25b51b604575996127545a83183e.JPG" /></p>
<p>I'm not so sure about the second one unfortunately. I may have waited too long before moving it into the growing medium? I see something that kinda looks like a cap of the seed, but not sure. Will give it time, maybe I didn't bury it deep enough?</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/ca9bfa5aa3d34dd59bc8c3dc659a8e64.JPG" /></p>
<p>Amnesia however is doing great!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/aebe68f9dcc74e3cb38ee5c8611e9035.JPG" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amnesia Survivor Seedling ]]></title>
            <guid>c4c1bcf08a374844a7ab3096fcdd73ca</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 16:30:06 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[She’s doing great so far! Excited to see how big her buds get!<br />
<img src="/_resources/fab4a168dd9545279e65fee1e447aff2.jpg" />]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Liberty Haze into trays]]></title>
            <guid>3c44e4ab32be4210a28eb34e9c09ab91</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 18:10:42 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Got the Liberty Haze seeds up and running! I started by filling up my seedling tray with worm castings. I figure it can help provide it a good start.</p>
<img src="/_resources/277dc3c9b85248938844284147625b0c.jpg" width="725" height="967" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>They both look healthy and strong! I’m excited for their growth!</p>
<img src="/_resources/a76eda77e20847a1bf1e7023406e65ae.jpg" width="717" height="956" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>Safely tucked away in their little nests to grow up big and strong!</p>
<img src="/_resources/519054d205bd4e4692c47da9eed94013.jpg" width="713" height="951" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>Now we just wait for them to sprout!</p>
<img src="/_resources/48060b7ed6334e3fbf38bdc6200ada64.jpg" width="710" height="947" class="jop-noMdConv" />]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Liberty Haze - moved seeds to paper towels ]]></title>
            <guid>088ddf3e50414e5d984e7f8bbe9347c1</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 02:32:17 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Moved them to wet paper towel</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/c19e885c5cd44b339ad8702dfd113ad3.jpg" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amnesia disaster]]></title>
            <guid>ba7efdf59b8849198751760772b93cf0</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 18:56:09 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Because of my negligence, 2 of the 3 seedlings died in the seedling trays. An expensive lesson learned ($20). An additional lesson learned is to be careful when adding seeds to water. Make sure you put the water in first, not vice versa. Thankfully, the two new seeds are ok and floating in water currently. They will be put into paper towels soon! The two new seeds are Liberty Haze.</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/0684395d30e74659916807911ddac296.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/22a6e8fb0c0c40e689169d3c38a23721.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/b907c40e7de54dbc9fb4dcc6b625c4ba.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/a17748ff36184d44ac6f0168dfb77d56.jpg" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prepping soil for Amnesia seedlings to transplant]]></title>
            <guid>fe2dadd122674c92a1ec61a674c7fb43</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 15:45:27 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday I realized I had a piece of wood laying around that was the perfect width for the shelf slot on my Costco shed. I cut it to the right length, and bam I have a gardening shelf in my bike shed!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/9126d4fa138e478fa8711cdbe6bd2a5a.jpg" /></p>
<p>I took the old dirt and cleaned out the old plants from it.<br />
<img src="/_resources/aee2855fd6fb454688b056142a8a5e50.jpg" /></p>
<p>I then mixed in a half trowel of earthworm castings as fertilizer to recharge the soil. I’ll be using nutrients too so I think we will be fine recycling the dirt.<br />
<img src="/_resources/d18e5a713d4548a6b091861586799a70.jpg" /></p>
<p>We then planted our little seedlings!<br />
<img src="/_resources/4047ff60f2844313a79583f0902584ff.jpg" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amnesia Seed sproutlings ]]></title>
            <guid>ddcf348fcf384e79bdaf1fd635e783e2</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 04:52:51 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>They are looking good!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/6f3960d52dc0413e90f54cb029efe763.jpg" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amnesia Seedlings starting to sprout]]></title>
            <guid>6e1541bff98b46799b46ccff87bc5739</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 03:35:09 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ChatGPT is saying that they should be ready for harvest between <strong>November 10, 2023, and December 1, 2023</strong>. We put them in water on August 25th.</p>
<p>Excited to see how they look! Going to start a grow journal for this plant and hopefully do a better job of tracking it.</p>
<p>We still need to order more rocket fuel.</p>
<p>We need to figure out a better automated water situation? Specifically the lid of the existing bag keeps coming off which could contaminate the water. I should 3d print something that allows air to go through but not bugs and dust.</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/446640d5256b40c5baa2ebeaeae23fb7.jpg" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Growing Products that I bought to start my growing journey]]></title>
            <guid>865da6512f6b47c6a2d4081de169ad69</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 00:30:24 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I didn't have a green thumb before this, but it was a cool learning experience. I started by growing with no nutrients and walmart soil, and the results were pretty sad. I slowly upgraded from there. I watched a ton of youtube videos and after 3 grows, I'd say I finally feel like I kinda sorta know the beginning's of what I'm doing lol. Tara likes training the plants to grow sideways so you get multiple mega buds at the top instead of just 1. We got like 6 off one plant this time, it was awesome! And kinda therapuetic, like doing a bonzai. If you haven't grown before, these are the things I can't live without now.</p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th>Image</th>
<th>Name</th>
<th>Description</th>
<th>Cost</th>
<th>Link</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><img src="/_resources/aaf35d47bdac42449fd89d9478b26ecd.png" /></td>
<td>Automated Pump</td>
<td>Decent pump I leave plugged in. I run it for 3 minutes everyday and that works pretty well</td>
<td>$29.99</td>
<td><a title="https://amzn.to/44y0Isx" href="https://amzn.to/44y0Isx">Amazon Link</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><img src="/_resources/555343a276c44377b80038f07903884a.png" alt="2102099f0c1238549dabfdc1f365670f.png" width="168" height="156" class="jop-noMdConv" /></td>
<td>Water Bag</td>
<td>Using this bag with the pump, I go about a week without having to water the plants:</td>
<td>$15.24</td>
<td><a title="https://amzn.to/3L6aKKC" href="https://amzn.to/3L6aKKC">Amazon Link</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><img src="/_resources/0ce4a3644a7c4acc9014383267ade1e1.png" /></td>
<td>Rogue Fuel</td>
<td>This soil has all the nutrients you need so you don't absolutely need nutrients, but if you use the nutrients, they help make the buds ridiculously big.</td>
<td>$45.68</td>
<td><a title="https://amzn.to/47XQHaW" href="https://amzn.to/47XQHaW">Amazon Link</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><img src="/_resources/4dc8fc7ec10a457385cab37f0986e0e7.png" /></td>
<td>Grow Big by Fox Farms</td>
<td>These are the nutrients I am using. I did a grow without them and one with and the difference was astounding. After the leaves come out I used grow big in the middle for pretty much all of it.</td>
<td>$41.99</td>
<td><a title="https://amzn.to/3Z02tO2" href="https://amzn.to/3Z02tO2">Amazon Link</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><img src="/_resources/1c464cca262d4404823ef37c88b0f0fe.png" /></td>
<td>Cal Mag</td>
<td>If you use shitty soil like I did at first, you may get big white spots on your leaves, this fixes it:</td>
<td>$20.19</td>
<td><a title="https://a.co/d/2HZfeGW" href="https://a.co/d/2HZfeGW">Amazon Link</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><img src="/_resources/526e12ec8a2c4e0bb941d87d2c5b7fa0.png" /></td>
<td>Grow Tent</td>
<td>I used this tent, I can fit like 4-5 big 7 gallon plants in this one:</td>
<td>$108.12</td>
<td><a title="https://amzn.to/3sugSFZ" href="https://amzn.to/3sugSFZ">Amazon Link</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><img src="/_resources/dee2b8f4c0e942fc9f60f55a88c34dd6.png" /></td>
<td>Grow Light</td>
<td>This is the light I use, it is really strong, and you can kinda see it peaking out the seams of the tent. I can't close the tent because it gets too hot out here.</td>
<td>$139.99</td>
<td><a title="https://amzn.to/3P0RKym" href="https://amzn.to/3P0RKym">Amazon Link</a></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>Total Cost: $401.20</p>
<p>I have a bunch of other stuff now, like thermometer, and shit, but I think everything else is extra, this is like the minimum I need to grow. Next I'm going to put a greenhouse on our land with AC to do a much bigger grow, but not just of cannabis, but food too. My ADHD super power is automation (or being lazy as shit lol) so I want to apply that to the greenhouse so we can still travel.</p>
<p> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maui Waui Grow Photos]]></title>
            <guid>29aaac470422475180f681c4a4dfea01</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This was our most successful grow yet! The final dry yield was 41.54 gs total harvest which has a value of $415.40 at dispensary prices.</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/522ef44df5294e06ac720dcd3ca68d01.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/22be276e44c74a32931d9095195c2866.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/291c41c0bed24550be2ea87fa3492ee8.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/95b39b33c18040839876c61895c71712.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/f0bf0095af00446eb9f4865c472ad342.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/e2ed428891f049fbb7e18aba5b1d9e1c.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/7b5ccbe539ae466cb7108bb955c41288.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/2b36aa18add040f5839992acb11ccf0d.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/fef0c9fc8587490d8cb6afbb27a7aa78.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/1de6ac18f88e48de9f93fec20019b75c.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/5c8d1f85e6ab4a78a62562a299c6880b.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/bd2f195f316844c2b488cca45544fb64.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/942b59489eaa42ddbca9902d50cf04ca.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/de54585aa162474d9635151b1896fd4f.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/fe592bdaded4482f91ea6915fca76fdd.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/54db979f62774ffb8130567a28dec0d8.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/c7adff5b69fb43c8980572e5d9cc1b08.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/bcdc5a6b1874479f9f672493186c00ab.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/ce443b1195eb403a9ea10884ca21b78a.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/4f9ea43eb6c841868f4fcd9cc22f8a98.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/b6665e8219ad493ea3d1cd5e5072786b.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/41526fb8e6ef495fb08665b09148e46a.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/22e0af8989ab43d09a0cf18720dfaabc.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/6df600269f11460aae3e5e6246a4e23f.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/2f383980cf944292a320f1581ab8edd3.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/f27fedaf20594453a2705d55d4a7692f.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/b994935fcad440abafeba40617c333f3.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/e7e03a0ba6c14c9d816375447fb8353b.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/653ae291e0874255b997792538803ad5.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/1b2d70772e154843b1c7ba1cbf8e089e.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/86a4167b9cae41b58a7d2a29eca89f2d.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/c4de75ef25ae48f294cf18a496dd9b49.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/31556e8cb72a4d03b183890aa46807e0.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/dfc4bb6905e246f3b0cac9663b7738c4.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/5ea3f34d606946599b625d236a25296f.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/7f33afab38574a0fbb520f2546556c6b.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/cab2bba456cb48a7be744fe43df9ec56.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/fc8f683a0a3d49158196e34afc79acf7.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/8fd197a74d1d457abe8cf5b598ac3533.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/23d1496c05a7418a9c6ce517f289f238.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/04eac20ac5cb4721a645dcfb13cfec0f.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/5f04fa22efc541298de315cd46e56138.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/65801b48e4e34519bac41671ae9c60a1.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/00576816eb2440f9802f9cdae76972ca.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/b989e63b3fc04c8fb3d128f0fa07b507.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/2b27bd30485b49aab97bb48def0fcbd9.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/75d8ed299f5c42ad80a3295aad7b0905.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/365aefb7c15f4dd79f2f6d127e3980fe.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/ca4efe41384f4f4aba5fb23d3e24b754.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/714ee3b0f4a0494f9c541edf967e7dc7.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/ca7fb8bd1d0d4101882f5730e91a7198.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/e57fe0d65a80416b96d276c97dd0dc36.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/133c7108ca2b4661af3485d7791f4bbe.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/0129b6d784644a0ebbfe9a02c49a7436.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/e0f58bf12da14d9c98e265e5db8c1399.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/07049ed8f6954dcf94dc943b6008793b.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/0496469e22cb46b091722ede26979b61.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/ba5b4b1d06264ae8b3609971ee9b8b62.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/d19e72eda5bf47eca8905a9bf0fe1606.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/46727cf851514a7aa479b2a81c02b46f.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/30ee3dbee8464df08540b4494ded4dc5.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/8d9842697d374606aedac1f54d5418da.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/0c19c2052f0c46a5890106d4e795c0e6.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/2e7099360f634db78b089e3549714050.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/aa0035965bda4630b779663975f53b14.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/94b9610bce8245fdaef77ecfdb764bd8.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/424420cfdf6b498c9fbfeaf98891dd8e.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/9632fa8a63364044b5db5665bfe4c006.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/b16f6d9e0e8f47d893db0e0d16790c3b.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/b9830defac814e4d8a86800baf043353.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/b55863af2f374b33a4a27fbb727828f2.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/a6a1ef44b6e74751a871114c251034a3.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/5abe8b80d55a408ab1899d0bbd2e00a7.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/9ccb83def5094eef9ab159f8268e85d1.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/07b254304e6c44308814f257a7e63e05.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/1d72b17b975c43248c82a8359ac50e03.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/d8c16ec5ce5f4421ae8dc50e87008c2e.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/6fbddad4704648019809a5081f9d07f9.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/e8d616aaf62844adb66d8b5cdb9f02f3.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/14365541edd2458a973c705d7f7b91e1.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/36f4ff9bf40f4f65a6ca960eb9f444d1.jpg" /></p>
<p>The final product! It smells so good! Only criticism is that I did a lazy job of trimming so there is a good amount of sugar leaves on it. But it tastes wonderful!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/0d7002335dc8413c830b0efe53050398.jpg" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cannabis Growth Terminology]]></title>
            <guid>17d42112a33447659b3252408a812a7e</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I use the image below to get my language correct:</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/b2e64e07d4b84412a8f9fd3f2e12f208.png" /></p>
<p> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>