<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title></title>
        <link>undefined</link>
        <description>undefined</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:56:27 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Joplin Pages Publisher</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Haircut for the ladies]]></title>
            <guid>fc3cac9d49fd4d22b33a2b39fbdb49e0</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 06:37:11 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The ladies got a little trim tonight!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/9f81aa28f2a54ab7a38d6f25b8a1b8cc.png" /></p>
<p>As always, my nesty does an amazing job! The trim looks great and I hope it gives energy to the other buds!</p>
<p>I went ahead and put the link to the spreadsheet I use in the home page to make it easier for myself and others to keep track of my different grows.</p>
<p>Haze is about a month away from Harvest and her buds are looking amazing. Here are some closeups!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/219cb8471f7b4608a33321819e21cbca.JPG" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/15f31c6a8f8c447cab3efbfb5aee3db0.JPG" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/d892164372bc4adeafa9583fe7d420c9.JPG" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Seeds have arrived!]]></title>
            <guid>e38268769c19474fa3bc9c29d8362222</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 16:12:31 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src="/_resources/b092b227f6bd4a62942d528ec31b6fd7.jpg" /></p>
<p>I finally got our order from Seedsman! We ordered the white widow and got the rest for free as a special:</p>
<ul>
<li>White widow
<ul>
<li><img src="/_resources/0ff9e14827f6494689290f99224b79a9.jpg" /></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Alaskan purple auto
<ul>
<li><img src="/_resources/c862184d476e48f79541956b97d48b01.jpg" /></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>OG Kush Auto
<ul>
<li><img src="/_resources/664252244f484a3b8e99571690005e06.jpg" /></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Witches Wedding
<ul>
<li><img src="/_resources/89bbea389aa7410d8d80a6d018fa8b3d.jpg" /></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Here are some photos of the girls from today!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/86141d8f8e9a4051bb200a71718a0c10.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/bd90b405b98c4d11a7970ee89064f3cc.jpg" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/8e34983995e04ecbacc0238585754f13.jpg" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automated Water tank refill]]></title>
            <guid>35e882a9aa43408abca6deb4bd7b93ce</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 16:36:54 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src="/_resources/71b0e9c7552049b1bb9d493e7a680fce.jpg" /></p>
<p>The girls are still doing well! Here is their grow schedule:</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/0de74d47ab86452a9478d18ecbbc2a7c.jpg" /></p>
<p>While I was checking on them, I noticed that my watering bag is almost empty! That means we had 8 days of automatic watering. However we did give nutrients (grow big) separately. The automated watering is nice but it’s only really useful when we are gone. While here we give it the nutrients to ensure the buds grow nice and fat.</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/a944176bde034fcdb4b714fea2c3dfde.jpg" /></p>
<p>The girls happy to see their water tower full!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/102181e3be684d0c82d04be911812b04.jpg" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automation Nation]]></title>
            <guid>ec4328be48c341f3b2c324cd001378bb</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 16:44:30 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I was finally able to sit and focus on automating our grow last night! I think the thought of travel has me wanting to ensure that if we do go anywhere, we don't have to rely on relatives to water the plants.</p>
<p>I started first by simply putting the old setup back in place, but immediately noticed that 2 of the 6 outlets were not putting out water. Here is a photo of one of the ones that was working.</p>
<img src="/_resources/4ee43cbe335f4f54b9a8431a07af0ed7.JPG" alt="IMG_7664.JPG" width="803" height="603" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>I figured the issue was related to how long the hose was and how chaotic it was setup. I sat down and began to trim and optimize the path of water for each plant, ensuring that each plant got just enough length of hose to fit in the pot comfortably. Here is a picture of all the hose we were able to avoid using! We removed one outlet as we only needed 5.</p>
<img src="/_resources/d2e40c8c125546d48eb7b7628bd71202.JPG" alt="IMG_7667.JPG" width="586" height="440" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>That left us with this setup!</p>
<img src="/_resources/55257aada7334b4ea68763967966fc8f.JPG" alt="IMG_7668.JPG" width="724" height="543" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>As you can see, I have my 5 gallon water bag on the left, and I have it set to water the plants for 3 minutes every day. Since I'll be home to monitor the output, I plan on adjusting this timing as needed, and every two days manually water in a circular pattern to encourage diverse root growth. I don't want the roots to congregate only around one spot where the drip system is for the whole grow, but at least while I'm traveling or on days I forget it's not a big issue.</p>
<p>As you can see, the nutrient burn is getting better by the day on Haze! I'm flushing the soil out with only water slowly, and it's definitely helping. I think I should be doing a much bigger flush of water, but I don't want to stress the plant too much.</p>
<p>Here is a final picture for today of my babies! As you can see, haze is getting really close! I also took the time to blow the dust out of my fan, it looks a lot cleaner now!</p>
<img src="/_resources/cbed5e2c502d4126b0a0c04d96e7effb.JPG" alt="IMG_7665.JPG" width="845" height="634" class="jop-noMdConv" />]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nutrient Burn and Organization]]></title>
            <guid>ce5e2ca49faa4509afab18e9ef66397d</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 05:47:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I recently realized that some of my stress with growing was not having the information I needed at hand. For example when I needed to harvest, among other things, so being a total nerd, I went ahead and created a spreadsheet. I clipped the notes section, but you get the idea.</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/9e9af7c0f84c4494b0df2bed9f2fe163.png" /></p>
<p>From there, to be able to tie the plant itself to the data, we gave them names and labels.</p>
<img src="/_resources/38858a2678e14f3fb3d56ce86ab465ef.JPG" alt="IMG_7659.JPG" width="512" height="384" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>Which made me feel so good, to see the garden all tagged properly:</p>
<img src="/_resources/5dfe7da9543243c6a3360b417f5c37c9.JPG" alt="IMG_7660.JPG" width="816" height="612" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>With so many plants to care for, I need to get my automatic watering pump back up and running. To that end, I finally DIY'ed a solution to the hose cover that fits perfectly. I had previously put a water gallon lid on the water jug, but it didn't fit well and would fall off, encouraging algae growth. I finally used a sharp blade to cut out the sides of the water cap, and replaced it with the actual lid that came with the jug, but with the spout portion removed. It now looks like this:</p>
<img src="/_resources/1979bf8e688143e5a24c9c1aaa36f526.JPG" alt="IMG_7661.JPG" width="715" height="716" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>One of the other things we've been dealing with as well is nutrient burn. I think I aggressively gave the plants too much nutrients and Haze developed a yellow splotchy color on the leaves. I've gone ahead and switched to only water to flush out the soil, and it seems to be working out great! Photo on the left is from today, and the right is 4 days ago:</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/7c35b93a918c4fcbafa44861416bae1a.png" /></p>
<img src="/_resources/be5680b6ef6a4aa481b729b5193a3680.JPG" alt="IMG_7653.JPG" width="795" height="795" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>Otherwise, the new seedlings are getting along great!</p>
<img src="/_resources/4a20b30fd2eb4a16a1767446ebd6a4f8.JPG" alt="IMG_7654.JPG" width="789" height="828" class="jop-noMdConv" />]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Northern Lights Seedlings!]]></title>
            <guid>7107d10e5854478387557bdb1edf0d4f</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src="/_resources/6ce7752e4b434d2db72020fe797509f0.jpg" /></p>
<p>New little sproutlings!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/b99e5b067d9f4a929a56456c70fa139e.JPG" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amnesia and White Widow Photo Dump and updates!]]></title>
            <guid>02498bb12bc84b4187d35f811a6a3a7f</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 20:33:34 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The plants are growing nicely! Here is a group of photos from the White Widow plant I've started nicknaming Runty:</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/240f3381af544d41933ad3d85e8da693.png" /></p>
<p>When she first started her growth, a piece of the seed stayed on like a hat, but it has since finally fallen off and she is growing great!</p>
<p>All these photos are from the end of Sept until now, the middle of October.</p>
<p>Next up is Amnesia! She's doing great and recently got a trim and we began training her on the netting! Very excited to see the growth!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/a1c2679a727b470a91c93087cc9999be.png" /></p>
<p>And last is Runty's sibling, who is definitely an overachiever:</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/0ac681a0be084dd0b1069e10008ace39.png" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amnesia and White Widow Update]]></title>
            <guid>7d3541e155124d2d8d33cf3dd047f1a4</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 17:45:56 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amnesia is doing good! I think it may still need some more nutrients due to the yellowish sheen, but I think overall it's doing great! Here is a photo from a few days ago</p>
<img src="/_resources/e45c0160384e4be5ba56f9f60225da3e.JPG" alt="IMG_7019.JPG" width="644" height="483" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>And here is one today. As you can see, quite a bit of growth!Pl</p>
<img src="/_resources/a6357048bd3d40d08c42f07c373f1887.JPG" alt="IMG_7252.JPG" width="635" height="846" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p>I'm still a bit sad about the loss of our Liberty Haze, but happy that our White Widow seeds are kicking butt! Here are photos from when we transferred the seeds to the trays yesterday:</p>
<img src="/_resources/6efb5eb4a8954b478a7f926931b04b88.JPG" alt="IMG_7249.JPG" width="623" height="467" class="jop-noMdConv" />
<p> <img src="/_resources/3c299af89ac948d98c6a0a74cb120b36.JPG" alt="IMG_7251.JPG" width="615" height="820" class="jop-noMdConv" /></p>
<p><img src="/_resources/5047acad34924908b303dec12c91f55a.JPG" alt="IMG_7250.JPG" width="620" height="826" class="jop-noMdConv" />  <img src="/_resources/0278616aa0a5467b908ff6213ed13380.JPG" alt="IMG_7253.JPG" width="625" height="833" class="jop-noMdConv" /> <img src="/_resources/fb1f3cfed023466ab426af38aba6a640.JPG" alt="IMG_7254.JPG" width="619" height="826" class="jop-noMdConv" /></p>
<p>And here are the seeds today! As you can see, they are ready to rock and roll!</p>
<img src="/_resources/940025d5b98c46a4845f7b4fceeea562.JPG" alt="IMG_7290.JPG" width="642" height="856" class="jop-noMdConv" />]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[White widows transferred to napkin!]]></title>
            <guid>9e47ee0bd13f457888275d28df8a1bbb</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 05:56:54 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Got it done!</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/79e7b198f8af4c7080ac14f9ed6739e8.jpg" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Good bye Liberty haze and hello white widow ]]></title>
            <guid>5b40656ae560417cbf69130f71eb1e33</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 15:54:06 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It looks like mold got to the Liberty haze seeds. I think I put too much water in the seedling tray which over saturated the seeds and led to mold growth. RIP.</p>
<p>Lesson learned, now on to white widow, which are our last seeds so we will need to order some more.</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/c38daf70090e456491b390c8a00eff4c.jpg" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>